https://www.lact-aid.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
View Cart
My Account
Home
What is Lact-Aid?
Facts about Lact-AidWhen to use Lact-Aid
About Lact-Aid
The Lact-Aid StoryPrivacy PolicyReturn PolicyWarrantyShipping Time
Blog
Online Library
FAQ About Nursing Adoptive BabiesRelactation: One alternative to untimely weaningWhat Health Practitioners and Mothers have said about Lact-AidHelpful hints using your Lact-Aid Nursing Trainer SystemOvarectomy, HRT and Breastfeeding Adopted InfantsBibliography
Links
Contact Us
Love Letters
Wholesale
Order Products:
Trainer Systems
Additional Trainers
Trainer Parts
System Parts
Accessories
4oz. Nursing Bags
7oz. Nursing Bags
Privacy Policy
By using the Lact-Aid International website, you consent to the privacy policy outlined below.Collection of your Personal InformationLact-Aid International collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number when you place an order on our website. We use this information to ship you products and get in touch with you if necessary.
Lact-Aid also reserves the right to email you with updates about our products and anything else that we feel may be important to you.We have a collection of web links on our site and it should be noted that Lact-Aid is not directly affiliated with any other websites. Lact-Aid International is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of www.lact-aid.com.Use of CookiesThe Lact-Aid International Web site uses "cookies" to remember things like your login and password and the contents of your shopping cart. These cookies are a convenience for our customers and do not contain anything that would harm your computer.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Please be aware that without cookies you will not be able to checkout using our online shopping cart.Security of your Personal InformationLact-Aid International secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Lact-Aid International secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted through our secure payment processor, it is protected through the use of industry standard 128-bit encryption, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementLact-Aid International will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Lact-Aid International encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Lact-Aid International is protecting your information.Contact InformationLact-Aid International welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Lact-Aid International has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Lact-Aid International using the Contact Us link on the top menu.
© 2020 Lact-Aid International. All rights reserved.
Privacy Statement |
Terms Of Use |
Copyright |
Contact
